This video introduces a long-established buffet restaurant in Guangzhou
while driving through Tianhe, Guangzhou.
You can also take the subway
from Guangzhou Tower
to Guangzhou Panyu District
. Go to Nancun Nanbo Station for a buffet
and queue up to enter the restaurant.
Lunch buffet: 178 yuan each, 108 yuan for seniors and 89 yuan for children.
It is a very large restaurant with
, go around
the children's candies,
chocolate fountain,
sashimi , salmon
line up, salmon
shark
fin fish with rice, Hong Kong style shark fin
fish
with rice
, Buddha jumps
over the wall, vegetarian abalone,
seafood shrimp
, frozen shrimp Frozen crabs
are cooked on the stove,
super gourmet
meatballs
, salad,
beef in golden soup
, cooked crayfish
a lot of delicious food and a choice of
fried steak.
Live seafood, grab
a piece of steamed oyster
stew cake ,
fruit
drink area
in the hot pot
barbecue area
The condiment area
is a huge underground parking lot.
The navigation is also wrong.
This large underground parking lot must be noted that the parking space
is too big and it is easy to get lost.
We once tried to get lost in the underground parking lot.
This is
the parking lot of
Panyu's largest commercial center shopping mall food area.
It's so big that it's hard to find my car. I ca
n't remember which floor I parked on.
Enter the license plate and see where
I finally found the car.